LOGAN COLLINS

Senior Front-End Developer

\ +1-516-654-4426

@ hermes8527@gmail.com

Lyons, GA

@ logan-collins-portfolio.onrender.com

EXPERIENCE

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Brewlabs

= 04/2023 - 03/2024

Phttps://brewlabs.info/

- Created the company landing page using React from the Figma design, featuring simple yet elegant components and smooth animations
- Created UI kit and unit test script to expedite front-end development for landing pages and on-chain services such as staking
- Implemented UI of Staking and Zap-In page and collaborated with Smart Contract engineers to integrate Web3
- Collaborated with company executives to improve performance and service utilities and expand community

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

SparkWorld*

= 04/2022 - 03/2023

- Worked in the front-end development team of 5 members to build the company landing page in React
- Led a team of four front-end developers to develop the front-end of NFT Marketplace and Aggregator using the test-driven development approach
- Collaborated with Smart Contract engineers to integrate Web3 to buy NFTs through NFT Marketplace and Aggregator
- Used RESTful APIs provided by back-end developers with Swagger to get sale data and update transaction history

Senior Full Stack Blockchain Developer

Satang Technologies

= 04/2020 - 03/2022

- Collaborated with a designer to create a modern, yet simple user interface for our company's landing page
- Developed individual components and composed them to implement pixel-perfect frontend from Figma design
- Took part in Asset Tokenizer project as a front-end developer and collaborated with Smart Contract engineer to utilize real-estate transaction on blockchain

Senior Full Stack Developer

Polisport

= 04/2019 - 03/2020

https://polisport.com/, https://polisportvirtualtour.com/

- · Joined the company as a Full Stack Web Developer
- Collaborated with backend developers to retrieve products and services data for implementation of a pixel-perfect frontend in React from Figma Design
- · Wrote unit test scripts for the front-end using Mocha and Jest libraries
- Led Polisport Virtual Tour Project and implemented main UI in React and virtual tour in 3d environment using Three.js library

Full Stack Developer

Canary Technologies

= 04/2016 - 03/2019

A https://glassbororentals.com/, https://ventano.de/

- During my six-month internship as a developer, I gained valuable insights into the company's culture and development methodologies
- In the Glassboro Rentals project, I created smooth and visually appealing user interfaces as a front-end developer
- Designed MySQL database and contributed to three pages using Laravel framework as a Full Stack Developer in the Ventano project

SUMMARY

A seasoned front-end developer with 8+ years of experience in the web development industry. What sets me apart is the ability to learn new technologies, passion for the product and keen eye for detail.

I always create detailed workflows, progress stepby-step, and conduct thorough testing to ensure accuracy and timely development.

I enjoy proposing new ideas, wearing different hats, and collaborating with others to achieve success.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA **3.9 /** 4.0

DePaul Unversity

.:---- !!

SKILLS

Frameworks & Libraries

React	Red	ux Next.	js Vue	Lit
Laravel M		iterial UI	Bootstrap	
Tailwin	nd CSS	Web3		
Langua	ges			
JavaScript		TypeScript	PHP	
Develop	ment 8	Operation	S	
	Agi	le		
Scrum				
	Contro	l Systems		
Version		-	Bitbucke	et
Version	GitHub	-	Bitbucke	et

STRENGTHS

Time Management	
Communication	

Teamwork